-Enjoy yourself. Enjoy yourself.
Welcome, everybody.
Welcome, welcome,
welcome to "The Tonight Show"!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Thank you for being here.
I am very excited
about tonight's show.
Robert De Niro is here tonight!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Right now he's working on
"Meet the Parents 4."
[ Audience oohs ]
Backstage, I asked what's going
on with the Fockers?
And he said, "What did
Trump and Elon do now?"
And I go, "No, no, no,
no, the movie."
[ Laughter ]
Meanwhile, I saw
that Ariana Grande will be
in the new "Meet the Parents."
[ Audience oohs ]
And in return, Robert De Niro
will be in "Wicked 2."
[ Laughter ]
[ as De Niro ]
Something has changed within me.
Something has changed.
Something not the same.
[ Normal voice ]
Some political news --
Yesterday, President Trump was
on his way to Camp David
when it looked
like he had a little trouble
boarding Air Force One.
Watch this.
Whoop. There you go.
Yeah, Joe Biden was like,
"Not so easy, is it?"
Ah!
[ Laughter ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
That's what happens when
your necktie is eight feet long.
That's why --
[ Laughter ]
I'm not shocked that he tripped.
I'm shocked that he had
the upper body strength
to hold himself up.
[ Laughter ]
And then just a little
bit later, Secretary of State
Marco Rubio also made
his way onto the plane.
Let's see how that went.
[ Laughter ]
Oh, my God.
You know
Trump made Rubio trip just
so he wouldn't be the only one.
[ as Trump ]
Marco, you got to be --
You owe me a little favor,
buddy.
Come on, pal, make me look good.
Take one for the team, bud.
[ Normal voice ] Well, guys,
everybody's still talking about
Trump's feud with Elon Musk.
And apparently Trump
is considering getting rid of
the Tesla
that he bought a few months ago.
-Ooh!
-Although that's the same
feeling every Tesla owner has.
So...
[ Laughter ]
Giving up the car makes sense.
I mean, after a breakup,
you always get rid of things
that remind you of your ex.
It's like [as Trump]
"I want my vinyl back!
It's an original
Village People."
[ Laughter ]
[ Normal voice ] Can we see
how excited Trump was
when he bought his Tesla?
This is real.
-Thank you all very much.
I love Teslur.
[ Laughter ]
-But now Trump's
selling the car.
And check out how he's doing it.
Watch this.
-Come on down to Trump Teslur
where everything merst ger.
Where you can buy your
very own Teslur.
But we also have
Hondurs, Toyoturs,
Kiurs, Mazdurs, and Vulvas
all with 0% APR financing,
whatever the hell that means.
Trump Teslur. Stop in toder.
-Oh, yeah. Trump Teslur.
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ as Trump ] Get your Teslur.
[ Normal voice ] Everyone's
still talking about Trump's
big falling out with Elon Musk.
We've got so many questions.
So the president
actually agreed to join us
for an interview about it
right now.
Oh, thank you for being here,
Mr. President.
So, tell me what exactly
happened between you and Elon?
-We broke up a little bit.
-Okay.
Breakups are hard.
Things happen fast.
I mean, what were you saying
about Elon just last Wednesday?
-Is totally brilliant.
-Yeah.
And how about Thursday?
-He's dumb as a rock.
-Alright. Look. This --
[ Laughter ]
It must be tough.
Have you ever been
this disappointed by anyone
so close to you?
-Don Jr.
[ Laughter ]
And Eric.
-Alright, alright.
Speaking of kids, how many
of Elon's kids have you met?
-1.6 trillion.
Trillion, not billion.
-Okay, got it.
Now, your relationship
with Elon ended so abruptly.
Have you ever seen
anything explode this fast?
-Teslur!
-Alright. No. Okay.
Well, it looks like you're
going to need a new best friend.
Who do you think that'll be?
-Hannibal Lecter.
He's a wonderful man.
-Alright, forget it.
Let's just move on.
I heard that you might cut
Elon's SpaceX funding.
I mean, how would
you launch rockets without him?
-Bing bing bing boom, pshew!
It's gone.
-Okay. Okay. Last question.
How do you think Elon
is coping with the breakup?
-Hundreds of thousands
of dollars worth of cocaine.
[ Laughter ]
-Elon, is that true?
-Yes!
-Alright.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate this. Thank you.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Very busy.
-Wow.
I can't believe it.
-Well, switching gears
to some business news --
Lululemon is preparing to raise
prices after Trump's tariffs.
-Ooh.
-Yeah.
As a result,
Lululemon's stock is sagging,
but thankfully they can give it
a lift and make it look amazing.
[ Laughter ]
You guys see this?
Chipotle announced
that they're releasing their
first new dip in five years.
[ Audience oohs ]
They wanted to do it earlier,
but they had to wait
until RFK Jr shut down the FDA.
[ Laughter ]
This is real good.
You're going to love this dip.
Well, get this. Two
international researchers were
charged with smuggling fungus
into Michigan.
-Hold up, hold up.
You did not just say
"smuggling fungus."
-Yeah, Tariq. I did.
[ Band laughing ]
-That's crazy.
-What's so crazy
about smuggling fungus?
-That's the name
of our crunchy jam band,
our side project,
Smuggling Fungus.
-Oh, wow. I don't suppose
you'd want to play a song.
-One, two, three!
♪♪
-♪ Smuggling Fungus ♪
♪ We're Smuggling Fungus ♪
♪ Yeah, first we take
the fungus ♪
♪ And then we dip it in
the hummus ♪
♪ And then we take a compass ♪
♪ And we smuggle
all the fungus ♪
♪ Because we're
Smuggling Fungus ♪
-Wow, man.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Smuggling Fungus,
ladies and gentlemen.
Amazing. Good job.
And finally, a zebra
that had been lost in Tennessee
for the past week
was finally found
and flown back to its owner.
This is real. Take a look.
Zebra in a bag.
Or, as they call it at Arby's,
the number three.
[ Audience groans ]
By the way, that's also
how Trump plans to deport Elon.
We have a great show.
Give it up
for The Roots,
ladies and gentlemen.
♪♪
Nice.
Quickly here,
We just got some sad news.
The lead singer of Sly
and the Family Stone,
Sly Stone, passed away today,
one of the greatest
musical artists of all time.
So many songs, so many jams.
"Family Affair."
"Hot Fun in the Summertime."
-Yeah.
-Quest, you just recently made
a documentary about Sly
called "Sly Lives!"
It's on Hulu.
-Yeah.
-So, what was it like?
-I mean,
he's an absolute genius.
Like, he invented the alphabet
that all musicians write
their books with, you know?
-But he was also very reclu--
I mean, you couldn't --
No one could talk to him.
We didn't know where he was.
-It was hard extracting
information out of him.
-You did an amazing job.
He will be missed.
If you want to check out
what Questlove did,
it's on Hulu. It's called
"Sly Lives!" but we'll --
We will miss you.
Sly Stone, everybody.
[ Cheers and applause ]
One of the best.
Great, bud.
Guys, we have a fun show
for you tonight.
He's one of the greatest actors
of all time.
And he's a co-founder
of the Tribeca Festival,
which is celebrating
its 24th year.
It's running now
through June 15th.
So if you're in New York City,
get tickets right now.
Robert De Niro is here tonight!
[ Cheers and applause ]
The best.
What a show. The whole show.
-Come on!
-He is the highest selling
comedy recording artist
of all time.
His Bigger & Weirder
tour kicks off this Friday.
[ Cheers and applause ]
"Weird Al" Yankovic
is joining us tonight!
[ Cheers and applause ]
And we got great music
from Arcade Fire!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Robert De Niro, "Weird Al"
Yankovic, and Arcade Fire.
That is a show right there.
Come on! That's a hot show.
[ Cheers and applause ]